This is Wolverine. [IMG:left]
This is Deadpool. [IMG:right]
So what's the difference? [IMG:wtd]
Most people think Wolverine and [IMG:left]
Deadpool have the exact same [IMG:right]
healing factor.
They don't. [IMG:disagree]
Wolverine's natural mutant healing factor [IMG:left]
constantly fights off his heavy [IMG:left]
adamantium skeletal poisoning while [IMG:left]
repairing cellular damage. [IMG:left]
But Deadpool's artificial healing factor [IMG:right]
was cloned from Wolverine, but [IMG:right]
mutated by his aggressive cancer. [IMG:right]
Regenerating cells so fast, his [IMG:right]
body constantly replaces itself. [IMG:right]
Wolverine heals to survive his [IMG:left]
own bones, [IMG:left]
while Deadpool heals to stay alive. [IMG:remember_this]
Follow for more! [IMG:final_end]